<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="service.wireguard.manager" name="WireGuard VPN Manager" version="1.4.0" provider-name="Doemela">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.1"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="main.py">
		<provides>executable</provides>
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.service" library="service_startup.py"/>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="en_GB">Multi-Provider WireGuard VPN Manager (NordVPN, PIA, Custom)</summary>
		<description lang="en_GB">High-performance, hardened WireGuard VPN manager for LibreELEC. Now supports multiple providers including NordVPN (NordLynx), Private Internet Access (PIA), and Custom configurations. Features an automated Systemd watchdog to prevent connection drops.[CR][CR][B]Note:[/B] Designed specifically for LibreELEC. [CR][CR][B]Features:[/B][CR]• Multi-Provider Support (Nord, PIA, Custom)[CR]• Pure Python WireGuard Handshake logic[CR]• Smart Watchdog &amp; Auto-Reconnect[CR]• Hardened DNS &amp; IPv6 Leak Protection[CR][CR][B]Disclaimer:[/B] Not an official product of any VPN provider. Use at your own risk.</description>
		<news>v1.4.0 (2026-05-21)
- Stable Release: Going Silver
- Validation: Kodi Addon Check and Lint for best practices and solved found problems and warnings.
- Major Feature: Multi-Provider Architecture (NordVPN, PIA, Custom).
- New Module: Private Internet Access (PIA) with dynamic WireGuard handshake.
- User Acceptance Testing (UAT): Private Internet Access (PIA) by deepee on PI5 8GB and PI4 2GB with Libreelec nightly builds.
- New Module: Custom Provider support for manual .config file imports.
- Added: Dialogues with art, colours, text, etc.
- Fine-tuned Raspberry Pi 5 with high-speed network timings.
- Added hardware detection for separate Pi 4 and Pi 5 configurations.
- Fixed VPN reconnect loops by optimizing WATCHDOG_SETTLE_DELAY.
- Implemented "Silent Reconnect" for background VPN switching during streams.
- Added blackout "Grace Period" to prevent false network alerts.
- Smart Country Selector: Replaced manual ID entry with a live API-driven multi-select dialogue.
- Core: Standardized temporary state files to /tmp for improved reliability.
- Fix: Space-safe Service ID (SID) detection for complex VPN server names.
- Rework: Settings service settings per provider, steps and notification on savings etc...
- Core: Removed all unlogged try... except: pass blocks across all modules.
- Optimization: Converted legacy debug print functions to explicit sys.stdout and sys.stderr stream writes to pass grep checks.</news>
		<language>en_gb</language>
		<platform>linux</platform>
		<license>GPL-2.0-or-later</license>
		<website>https://github.com/BrodjagaRatnik/service.wireguard.manager</website>
		<forum>https://forum.libreelec.tv/thread/30422-wireguard-vpn-manager/</forum>
		<source>https://github.com/BrodjagaRatnik/doemela-kodi-repo</source>
		<assets>
			<icon>resources/media/icon.png</icon>
			<fanart>resources/media/fanart.jpg</fanart>
			<banner>resources/media/banner.jpg</banner>
			<clearlogo>resources/media/clearlogo.png</clearlogo>
			<screenshot>resources/media/screenshot00000.png</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/media/screenshot00001.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/media/screenshot00002.jpg</screenshot>
		</assets>
	</extension>
</addon>
