<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="service.wireguard.manager" name="WireGuard Manager NordVPN" version="1.2.1" provider-name="Doemela">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.1"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="main.py">
        <provides>executable</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service_startup.py"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en_GB">Hardened NordVPN WireGuard Manager for Raspberry Pi 5</summary>
        <description lang="en_GB">High-performance VPN manager for LibreELEC. Uses NordLynx for maximum speed with an automated Systemd watchdog to prevent connection drops.[CR][CR][B]Note:[/B] This addon is designed specifically for the LibreELEC filesystem and will not work on standard Android or Windows Kodi installations.[CR][CR][B]Features:[/B][CR]• WireGuard Native (NordLynx)[CR]• Smart Watchdog &amp; Auto-Regen[CR]• Hard Reset Routing Tables[CR][CR][B]Disclaimer:[/B] Not an official NordVPN product. Use at your own risk. This addon is provided "as is" without warranty. The developer is not liable for data loss or security breaches. Full disclaimer available in addon settings.</description>
        <news>v1.2.1 (2026-04-22)
- changes to Icon, screenshot images.
- FIXED service.py removed unused global variable

v1.2.0 (2026-04-21)
- IMPROVED settings.xml.

v1.1.9 (2026-04-20)
- ADDED (Auto-Healing): Watchdog automatically resets the retry budget when a physical network change (Eth/WiFi) is detected.
- ADDED (High-Visibility Alerts): Enhanced blackout notifications with Red/Bold formatting and custom ICON_ERROR support.
- ADDED (Intelligent Throttling): Helper now stands down after 10 failed attempts to preserve system resources and NordVPN API limits.
- ADDED (Smarter Connection Logic): Added pre-connection gateway validation to identify "No Internet" vs "VPN Handshake Failure."
- FIXED (Stability): Implemented a global lock-file to prevent Watchdog/Helper race conditions and "double-triggers."
- FIXED (Stability): Refined interface tracking to ignore virtual wg0 tunnels, ensuring the retry counter only resets on real hardware events.
- IMPROVED (Log Clarity): Reduced log levels for routine heartbeat checks to keep the system journal clean.
- IMPROVED (Performance): Increased polling frequency to 1Hz for near-instant physical disconnect detection.
- IMPROVED (Stability): Integrated aggressive "Double Stop" logic in a non-blocking thread to resolve player hangs faster.</news>
        <language>en_gb</language>
        <platform>linux</platform>
        <license>MIT</license>
        <website>https://github.com/BrodjagaRatnik/service.wireguard.manager</website>
        <source>https://github.com/BrodjagaRatnik/service.wireguard.manager</source>
        <assets>
            <icon>resources/media/icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>resources/media/fanart.jpg</fanart>
            <screenshot>resources/media/screenshot00000.png</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/media/screenshot00001.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/media/screenshot00002.jpg</screenshot>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>
