<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="service.wireguard.manager" name="WireGuard Manager NordVPN" version="1.0.4" provider-name="Doemela">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="main.py">
        <provides>executable</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service_startup.py"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en_GB">Hardened NordVPN WireGuard Manager for Raspberry Pi 5</summary>
        <description lang="en_GB">High-performance VPN manager for LibreELEC. Uses NordLynx for maximum speed with an automated Systemd watchdog to prevent connection drops.[CR][CR][B]Note:[/B] This addon is designed specifically for the LibreELEC filesystem and will not work on standard Android or Windows Kodi installations.[CR][CR][B]Features:[/B][CR]• WireGuard Native (NordLynx)[CR]• Smart Watchdog &amp; Auto-Regen[CR]• Hard Reset Routing Tables[CR][CR][B]Disclaimer:[/B] Not an official NordVPN product. Use at your own risk. This addon is provided "as is" without warranty. The developer is not liable for data loss or security breaches. Full disclaimer available in addon settings.</description>
        <news>v1.0.4
- Cleaned up logging
v1.0.3
- Cleaned up files and new icons
v1.0.2
- Security: Added automatic IPv6 Leak Protection. The manager now identifies and disables IPv6 on Ethernet and Wi-Fi.
- Routing Fix: Implemented Metric priority (Metric 100) for Ethernet to ensure VPN traffic always takes precedence.
- Hardware: Added Wi-Fi Kill Switch. Automatically disables Wi-Fi when Ethernet is connected to prevent multi-interface leaks.
- Setup: Improved first-run logic with a dedicated Keymap installation, mandatory Restart prompt, and Token Import wizard.
- Mapping: Slot assignments are now "Regen-Proof." They use Friendly Names (e.g., NordVPN_Belgium) instead of static IPs.
- UI: Synchronized notifications between the manual menu and background service, including progress bars and IP info lookups.
- Keymap: Removed the Blue button mapping from the keymap as it was found to be incompatible.
- Cleanup: Enhanced Factory Reset to purge NordVPN-specific configs and properly decommission legacy system services.

v1.0.1
- Added: Smart Add-on Mapping (Auto-connect VPN based on which TV add-on is open)
- Added: Visual Setup Wizard to easily assign WireGuard profiles to slots
- Added: Dynamic background monitoring for Kodi 21.3 (Omega)
- Improved: Log-less trigger detection for better performance on Pi 5
- Fixed: Resolved service-start delays in LibreELEC 12.2.1

v1.0.0
- Fixed: RunScript reinstall command argument parsing
- Improved: Main logic execution order for better setup handling
- Added: Enhanced logging for LibreELEC
        </news>
        <language>en_gb</language>
        <platform>linux</platform>
        <license>MIT</license>
        <website>https://github.com/BrodjagaRatnik/service.wireguard.manager</website>
        <source>https://github.com/BrodjagaRatnik/service.wireguard.manager</source>
        <assets>
            <icon>resources/media/icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>resources/media/fanart.jpg</fanart>
            <screenshot>resources/media/screenshot00000.png</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/media/screenshot00001.png</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/media/screenshot00002.png</screenshot>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>
